let questions = [ 
    {
        num: 1, 
        question: "Which nickname I have loved the most uptil now given by you??ü§îüíï",
        answer:"B. Tiddi",
        options:[
            "A. Bandarr",
            "B. Tiddi",
            "C. Gussamon",
            "D. Radio"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2, 
        question: "On which song did I first taught u dance?üíÉüï∫",
        answer:"C. Heeriye",
        options:[
            "A. What Jhumka!",
            "B. Tere Bina",
            "C. Heeriye",
            "D. Aa ke Dekhle"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3, 
        question: "When did we have our first fight?ü§îü§¶‚Äç‚ôÄÔ∏è",
        answer:"D. July",
        options:[
            "A. October",
            "B. December",
            "C. April",
            "D. July"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4, 
        question: "What was our plan on our first day of realtionship which you missed?",
        answer:"B. Bunk",
        options:[
            "A. Date",
            "B. Bunk",
            "C. Class",
            "D. McD"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 5, 
        question: "Where was the third time you gave a peck on my right cheek?ü§≠ü§≠",
        answer:"A. Lt",
        options:[
            "A. Lt",
            "B. Class backseat",
            "C. Auto to hapur",
            "D. Flat"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 6, 
        question: "What about the first on left one??üòÇü§®ü©µ",
        answer:"B. Holi Ghar",
        options:[
            "A. Auto",
            "B. Holi Ghar",
            "C. Class Backseat",
            "D. Library"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 7, 
        question: "What's according to you, is my idea of the perfect date night?(Jo kabhi baad me chalenge abhi nahiüòÇüòÇüòÇ)",
        answer:"B. Concert and outings",
        options:[
            "A. Candle-light dinner",
            "B. Concert and outings",
            "C. Movie night",
            "D. Gaming zone"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 8, 
        question: "Color of the first flower that I gave you?",
        answer:"D. White",
        options:[
            "A. Yellow",
            "B. Purple",
            "C. Red",
            "D. White"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 9, 
        question: "What is the first thing I do in the morning, when I'm with you?",
        answer:"B. Snuggle",
        options:[
            "A. Kiss your cheek..",
            "B. Snuggle",
            "C. Check for my phone",
            "D. Wake you up"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 10, 
        question: "What's my weirdest habit which you said you love the most??üòÇüòÇüòÇ",
        answer:"C. Doing random dance moves",
        options:[
            "A. Naming inanimate objects",
            "B. Collecting random items",
            "C. Doing random dance moves",
            "D. Speaking in different accents"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 11, 
        question: "Biggest hint giver to our relationship was..??",
        answer:"C. Sristhi",
        options:[
            "A. Trapti",
            "B. Laavanya",
            "C. Sristhi",
            "D. Jesmine"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 12, 
        question: "What weakness of mine gave me the best moment with you on the Manali Trip??üòçü©µ(gonna kill u for this one..)",
        answer:"D. Short height",
        options:[
            "A. Impatience",
            "B. Overthinking",
            "C. Lack of sleep",
            "D. Short height"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 13, 
        question: "Will I go out on an outing..Or will I choose my sleep over the outing?(until and unless me ekdum badiya..and not beemar)",
        answer:"A. Outing damn sure",
        options:[
            "A. Outing damn sure",
            "B. Neend bhaii neend",
            "C. Can't say moody ekdum",
            "D. Depends kab or kaha jaana hai"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 14, 
        question: "Only twinning that we decided in college to do?",
        answer:"D. Gray",
        options:[
            "A. Black",
            "B. Blue",
            "C. Red",
            "D. Gray"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 15, 
        question: "What was I wearing when you last met me now..??",
        answer:"C. Mahroon",
        options:[
            "A. Green",
            "B. Black",
            "C. Mahroon",
            "D. White"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 16, 
        question: "What's your contact photo on my mobile-phone?",
        answer:"D. Convocation",
        options:[
            "A. Christmas",
            "B. Farewell",
            "C. Trip",
            "D. Convocation"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 17, 
        question: "What color combo are 'you' and 'me' wearing in my whatsapp background image of your chat?",
        answer:"A. Blue and black",
        options:[
            "A. Blue and black",
            "B. Black and blue",
            "C. Black and mehroon",
            "D. Pink and white"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 18, 
        question: "The moment when I first time hugged you..??",
        answer:"A. Holi",
        options:[
            "A. Holi",
            "B. Date",
            "C. After returning from home",
            "D. Not these....June"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 19, 
        question: "Out of all true options, which is not my fetish?",
        answer:"B. Getting my friends into relationships",
        options:[
            "A. Randomly knowing bollywood movie dialogues",
            "B. Getting my friends into relationships",
            "C. Knowing every gossip",
            "D. Dancing to cheesy bollywood songs with correct steps"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 20, 
        question: "(Just Bonus)At What time you propsed me?",
        answer:"A. 12:23",
        options:[
            "A. 12:23",
            "B. 01:04",
            "C. 12:37",
            "D. 01:15"
        ]
    }
];